http://en.museobarracco.it/footer/privacy

Español
Legislative decree n.196 of 30.06.2003 has the aim of guaranteeing that personal data is used in a manner which respects rights, basic freedoms, including the dignity of the physical person, with particular reference to discretion and to personal identity.
In accordance with and in effect of legislative decree 196/2003 notice is given that:
- The personal data of the users of this site is collected and used in accordance with the procedures envisaged under the prevailing norms regarding the protection of personal data. Personal data can only be used for purposes previously declared to the users and on conditions that the users, in circumstances where authorization is required, have expressly authorized it.
- Specific security measures have been observed to prevent the loss of data, its unlawful or incorrect use, and unauthorized access.
- As regards the usage of the data collected, interested subjects can exercise the rights envisaged according to article 7-8-9-10 of the above mentioned legislative decree 196/2003. In particular they can obtain from the owner or from those responsible for the usage of the data confirmation of the existence or otherwise of their own personal data and have it made available to them in an intelligible form; they can be informed of the origins of the data, including the reason and purpose on which its use is based; they can obtain the cancellation of data used in violation of the law, including the adjournment, rectification or integration of data; they can also, for legitimate reasons, object to the usage.- The owner of the data, who is responsible for its use is the Zètema Progetto Cultura srl, whose offices are in Via Attilio Benigni, 59, 00156 Roma, e-mail info@zetema.it
#MuseoBarracco
The MiC APPs
I MiC sui social network
Il Museo Barracco si racconta grazie alla tecnologia del Google Arts & Culture
Tour Virtuali. Viaggio digitale tra cinque Musei in Comune e i loro capolavori
Foto in Comune
I like MiC
#DiscoverMiC
MuseoBarracco
05/12/2020
Donne deportate, scultura in calcare alabastrino (668-627 a.C.), Sala II - Arte egizia e m
Read More
Leer más
@museiincomune
10/12/2020
Madre e figlia: Tina e Lisa Bilotti, dipinto del 1981 di #AndyWarhol, Sala I, Museo Carlo Bilotti.
Leer más
Blog MiC
06/08/2020#cineCampidoglioPer #laculturaincasa è partita, in questi mesi, una nuova rubrica settimanale dei Musei Capitolini. Seguendo gli hashtag #cineCampidoglio e #setCampidoglio è stato ed è ancora possibile scoprire tutte le occasioni in cui il&#8230; <a class="read-more" href="https://museiincomuneroma.wordpress.com/2020/08/06/cinecampidoglio/">Continua a leggere <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>Read more
21/04/2020Rovine: Canti di pietraQual è la trama che rende il tessuto dell’essere umano così pieno di fili inestricabili, connessi l’uno all’altro a formare un disegno al contempo splendido e tragico? Luogo ideale per incontrare questo universo&#8230; <a class="read-more" href="https://museiincomuneroma.wordpress.com/2020/04/21/rovine-canti-di-pietra/">Continua a leggere <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>Read more
More
Not available
10/12/2020
Giornata internazionale dei diritti delle persone con disabilità 2020 – Museo Napoleonico
Leggi le recensioni su: Museo di Scultura Antica Giovanni Barracco
Museo di Scultura Antica Giovanni Barracco, corso Vittorio Emanuele 166/A - 00186 Roma - Tel. +39 060608 - Email: info.museobarracco@comune.roma.it
© 2017 Musei in Comune / Privacy / Exclusions of Responsibility / Credits / Website accessibility / XML-rss
